cincopa.com 2019-05-30

# Privacy Policy - Cincopa.com

**(Last Updated: March 5, 2019)**

By using the Site or the Products available through the www.cincopa.com Site (the "Product"), you consent to the privacy practices described in this Policy.

We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time. If we make any material changes to our Policy, we will post a new policy on our Site and update the “last updated” date set forth above. Therefore, we encourage you to check our Policy whenever you use the Product to see if it has been updated since your last visit.

**Information Collected.**

Cincopa is now GDPR-compliant, for more information visit Cincopa GDPR Compliance & Data Privacy FAQ. 

We collect two basic types of information with our Product, namely personal information and aggregate information.  As used herein, the term "personal information" means information that specifically identifies an individual (such as a name and e-mail address), and demographic and other information about an individual when directly linked to personally identifiable information.  A user name may be personal information if it includes personally identifying information such as a first and last name.

Our definition of personal information does not include “aggregate” information. Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category or users from which individual user identities have been removed. In other words, information on how you use our Product may be collected and combined with information about how others use the Product, but no personal information will be included in the resulting data. Aggregate data helps us understand trends in our users’ needs so that we can better consider new features or otherwise tailor our Product.  This policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of aggregate information, and we may share aggregate information about our users with third parties for various purposes, including to help us better understand and improve our Product, and for advertising and marketing purposes.

Those are the types of personal and other information we collect. You should refer to the rest of this Policy to see how we use, disclose and protect this information

_Information You Give Us._

We collect information you give us at various times when you register with us and use our Product. Examples include the following:

Registration and Transaction Information.  When you register to use the Product, we may collect various kinds of contact information about you including, for example, your name and e-mail address.  We may also collect demographic information that you provide to us.  You will also be asked to create a user-chosen ID and password for your use when accessing the Product. 

Submissions and Customer Service.  From time-to-time we may post surveys, contests or sweepstakes on our Product, which may request personal or demographic information and customer feedback.  Participation in these requests is completely voluntary and with each request you will have the choice of whether or not to participate and disclose information. 

_Automatically Collected Information._ __

We automatically receive certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, when you use the Product, our systems may automatically collect your IP address and the type of operating system or browser you use. We may also collect information pertaining to your account activity, information pertaining to the files accessed or used by you, and standard access information, such as the time and date of accessing the Product, and usage of the Product.  We use such information to help manage the effectiveness of our online advertising and to gather access information, for purposes such as compiling aggregated statistics about Product usage. 

We may also use cookie technology to collect information.  Among other things, the use of cookies enables us to improve our Site by seeing which areas and features are most popular; to count the number of computers accessing the Site; to personalize the Site and improve the Site experience; to record your preferences; and to allow you to visit the Site without re-entering your member ID and/or password. A cookie is a small amount of data, often including an anonymous unique identifier, which is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Most browsers automatically accept cookies as the default setting. You can modify the setting to reject cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit by editing browser options.  However, if a browser is set not to accept cookies or if a user rejects a cookie, some portions of the Site and the Product may not function properly.  For example, you may not be able to sign in and may not be able to access certain Site features or Products.

_No Information about Children._

Our Product is not intended to be used by children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly, directly or passively, collect information from children under the age of 13. If we create offers and products that make it appropriate to collect information from children under the age of 13, we will notify you of the change in this Policy.

**Use and Sharing of Information.** ****

_Internal Use of Personal information._ __

In general, we use personal information internally to process your requests or transactions, to provide you with information or support you request, to inform you about other information, events, promotions or products we think will be of interest to you, to facilitate your use of, and our administration and operation of, the Site and to otherwise serve our users and enable them to take maximum advantage of our Product. For example, personal information may be used: 

  * to request feedback and to enable us to develop, customize and improve the Site and our publications and products;
  * to conduct marketing analysis, to send you surveys or newsletters, to contact you about a third party's services, products, activities, special events or offers and for other marketing, informational, product development and promotional purposes;
  * to send you a welcoming email and to contact you about your use of the Site, to respond to your emails, submissions, comments, requests or complaints, to perform after-sales activities, to anticipate and resolve problems with our Product, to respond to customer support inquiries, for assistance with our product and site development, and to create and inform you of new products from Cincopa.com that better meet your needs; 
  * to notify contest winners; and 
  * for the specific purpose for which the information was provided.

You should review the following section to understand when Cincopa.com discloses personal information to non-affiliated third parties.

_Disclosure of Personal Information to third Parties._ __

Cincopa.com reserves the right to share aggregated demographic information about our customers, sales, and traffic to our partners and advertisers. We will not give, sell, rent, share, or trade any of your personally identifiable information, or the data that you store using our Product to any third party, except as outlined in our Terms of Use and in this privacy policy. We reserve the right to disclose such information to a third party only if (a) we have your express written consent, (b) we reasonably believe we are compelled by applicable state and federal laws, or (c) we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person, or other irreparable injury, including economic interests of a third party, requires disclosure of the information without delay.

Cincopa.com uses a third party vendor to manage all credit card processing, and may partner with other parties to provide specific services. Upon registration with Cincopa.com, we will share names and other contact information as necessary for the applicable third parties to provide these services. These parties are not permitted under their contract with us to store, retain, or use your information for purposes not directly involved with their service to Cincopa.com. Specifically, our contracts with such third parties prohibit the third parties from using your personal information for purposes of marketing or promotions.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, we reserve the right to share personally identifiable information in connection with an acquisition, merger, or sale of all or a substantial portion of our business, with or to a company in a substantially similar business, provided that the other company agrees to comply with this or with a reasonably comparable privacy policy. In the event of any such sale or merger, you will receive notice of any changes in such policy.

**Network and Information Security.** ****

Reasonable effort will be taken to prevent unauthorized release, corruption, or loss of your personal and project data. For example, we limit which employees at Cincopa.com have access to your personally identifiable information. Specifically, only employees who require your personally identifiable information to perform a specific task are granted access to such information. In addition, user data is protected with SSL encryption for transmission to Cincopa.com. No customer information is stored on Cincopa.com employees' personal computers. 

The servers on which all customer data and information is stored are kept in a secure environment, and may be archived elsewhere.  Our records are stored indefinitely, as are our archival backup copies.  While we have taken efforts to guard your personal information, we cannot guarantee that your information will not be disclosed or accessed by accidental circumstances or by the unauthorized acts of others.

Your account information and access to our Product is accessible only through the use of an individual user ID and password. To protect the confidentiality of personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of our Site and Product by any person using your account user ID and password. Please advise us immediately if you believe your account user ID and password have been misused. In addition, always logout and close your browser when you finish your session. Please note that we will never ask you to disclose your password in an unsolicited phone call or email.

To date, we have never had a situation in which to our knowledge any of our users' personal information has been compromised in any way, or in which any user's personal information has become public. If Cincopa.com learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Cincopa.com may also post a notice on the Site if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach, you should notify us at support@cincopa.com.

**Updating Personal Information.** ****

If your personally identifiable information changes in any way, we request that you provide us the means to correct or update this information as soon as possible. To do so, please email any and all changes to support@cincopa.com.

**Choice/Opt-Out.** ****

By using Cincopa.com, you understand that we may send you communications or data regarding the Products, including but not limited to (i) notices about your use of the Products, including any notices concerning violations of use, (ii) updates, and (iii) promotional information and materials regarding our products and site, via electronic mail.  We give you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving electronic mail from us by following the opt-out instructions provided in the message. In addition, Cincopa.com provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us or to remove your information from our database at any time by emailing support@cincopa.com with your specific request.

**Contacting Us.** ****

Any questions about this Policy should be addressed to support@cincopa.com.
